Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Musical arrangements, 1940s-2000s
  - "Pharaoh", undated (Box 252, Folder 20)
  - "Power and Glory", undated (Box 252, Folder 21)
  - "Psalm 23", undated (Box 252, Folder 22)
  - "Rebbe Elimelech", undated (Box 252, Folder 23)
  - "Rebbe Zingt", undated (Box 252, Folder 24)
  - "Rezel", undated (Box 252, Folder 25)
  - "Ro'e ve Roa", undated (Box 252, Folder 26)
  - "Rumania, Rumania", undated (Box 252, Folder 27)
  - "Russian Gypsy", undated (Box 252, Folder 28)
  - "Sabbath Prayer", undated (Box 252, Folder 29)
  - "Sano Duso", undated (Box 252, Folder 30)
  - "September Song", 2006 (Box 252, Folder 31)
  - "Shabbes", undated (Box 252, Folder 32)
  - Shlof Shoyn Mayn Kind", undated (Box 252, Folder 33)
  - "Sheyiboneh Beis HaMikdash", undated (Box 252, Folder 34-35)
  - "Sunrise, Sunset", 2006 (Box 252, Folder 36)
  - "Sweetest Dreams by Thine", undated (Box 252, Folder 37)
  - "Theo's Family Nigun", undated (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - "To Life!", undated (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - "A Tog Fun Nekome", undated (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - "Toiro Tzivo", undated (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - "Tomorrow Lies in the Cradle", undated (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - "Tumbalaika", undated (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - "Unter a Kleyn Beymele", undated (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - "Uva-u Ha-ovdim", undated (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - "Yankele", undated (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - "Yerakina", undated (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - "Yidl", undated (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - "Yo m'enamori d'un aire", 2004 (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - "Der Zinger Fun Noyt", undated (Box 253, Folder 13)
  - "Zol Shoyn Kumen Di Ge'ule", undated (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Recording Info, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Scores, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - In My Own Lifetime Recording Session Scores, 2006 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Voice, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Flute, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Clarinet, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Alto Sax, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - In My Own Lifetime, French Horn, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 7)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Tuba, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 8)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Violin II, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 9)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Viola, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 10)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Cello, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 11)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Piano, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 12)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Accordion, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 13)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Banjo, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 14)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Guitar, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 15)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Bass, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 16)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Bouzouki, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 17)
  - In My Own Lifetime, Drums/Percussion, 2006 (Box 254, Folder 18)
  - Partial Club Set List, undated (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - "Am Israel Hai", undated (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - "Edelweiss", undated (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - "I Am Free", undated (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man", undated (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - "If We Only Have Love", undated (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - "In My Own Lifetime", undated (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - "Little Bit of Luck", undated (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - "Love Bows", undated (Box 255, Folder 9)
  - "Mack the Knife", undated (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - "Man Into Egypt", undated (Box 255, Folder 11)
  - "Marieke", undated (Box 255, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Club Set Parts, undated (Box 255, Folder 13)
  - "Rich Man Bows", undated (Box 255, Folder 14)
  - "September Song", undated (Box 255, Folder 15)
  - "Vieux Amants", undated (Box 255, Folder 16)
  - "Zorba Bows", undated (Box 255, Folder 17)
  - "Amsterdam", undated (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - "The First Time", undated (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - "Goajira", undated (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - "Gypsy", undated (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - "Kagdaya Payan", undated (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - "Moon Over Bourbon Street", undated (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - "New Israeli Song", undated (Box 256, Folder 7)
  - "Russian Gypsy Song", undated (Box 256, Folder 8)
  - "Time In a Bottle", undated (Box 256, Folder 9)
  - "Tomorrow Lies In the Cradle", undated (Box 256, Folder 10)
  - Aaron Copland, Lincoln Portrait, undated (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Fiddler On the Roof, Mill Run Theatre - Niles, Illinois, 1972 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Fiddler On the Roof, Starlight Theatre - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1972 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - "Moishele, Main Fraind", undated (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Loose Papers, undated (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Various Notes, undated (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Various Piano Conductor Parts, undated (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Various Set Lists and Notes, undated (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - 1994 Appearance (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - 2013 Austrian Parliament Program (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - "Marieke" Score, undated (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Stempeniu Score, 1984 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Various Lyrics and Piano Parts, undated (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Various Piano Conductor Scores, undated (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Various Scores, undated (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Various Vocal with Piano Parts, undated (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - "Chasene Tanz", undated (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man", undated (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man" in Db, undated (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - "Man into Egypt", undated (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Various Lead Sheets, undated (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Various Loose Parts, undated (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - Various Piano Conductor Scores, undated (Box 259, Folder 7)
  - Various Piano Parts, undated (Box 259, Folder 8)
  - Various String Parts, undated (Box 259, Folder 9)
  - "Amsterdam", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - "Bikel Walk On", undated (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - "The Fiddler", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - "Guajira", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - "Hangover", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - "In My Own Lifetime", undated (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - "It", undated (Box 260, Folder 8)
  - "Jerusalem of Gold", undated (Box 260, Folder 9)
  - "Man Come Into Egypt", undated (Box 260, Folder 10)
  - "Marieke", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 11)
  - "Next", undated (Box 260, Folder 12)
  - "Old Folks", undated (Box 260, Folder 13)
  - "Opening", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 14)
  - "September Song", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 15)
  - "Those Were the Days", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 16)
  - "Those Were the Days (Chaser)", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 17)
  - "Those Were the Days (Old Version)", undated (Box 260, Folder 18)
  - "Tomorrow Lies in the Cradle", 1974 (Box 260, Folder 19)
  - "Dara Goi", undated (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - "Dobrivechir", undated (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - "Do You Remember", undated (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - "Jerusalem of Gold", undated (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - "Koloda Duda", undated (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - "Kudryavchik", undated (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Parts, undated (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - "Moon Over Bourbon Street", undated (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - "My Father Was Born", undated (Box 261, Folder 9)
  - "Niska Banja", undated (Box 261, Folder 10)
  - "Rastumani", undated (Box 261, Folder 11)
  - "September Song", undated (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - "Sjaj Mesece", undated (Box 261, Folder 13)
  - Songs of the Earth Material, 1967 (Box 261, Folder 14)
  - "Tel Aviv", 1991 (Box 261, Folder 15)
  - "Thalassa", undated (Box 261, Folder 16)
  - "The Thieving Magpie", undated (Box 261, Folder 17)
  - "Tino Mori" and "Sua Nok Le Nada", undated (Box 261, Folder 18)
  - Various Bass Parts, undated (Box 261, Folder 19)
  - Various Piano Accompaniment Parts, undated (Box 261, Folder 20)
  - Various Piano Parts, undated (Box 261, Folder 21)
  - Various Viola Parts, undated (Box 261, Folder 22)
  - Various Woodwind Parts, undated (Box 261, Folder 23)
  - "Zvyozdochka - Little Star", undated (Box 261, Folder 24)
  - Brel is Alive, undated (Box 262, Folder 1)
    Includes one audiocassette.
  - Brel is Alive, About Brel, undated (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Brel is Alive, "The Bulls", undated (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Brel is Alive, "The Desperate Ones", undated (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Brel is Alive, "Fanette", undated (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - Brel is Alive, "Funeral Tango", undated (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Brel is Alive, "The Girls and the Dogs", undated (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - Brel is Alive, "Jackie", undated (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - Brel is Alive, "If We Only Have Love", undated (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - Brel is Alive, "I Loved", undated (Box 262, Folder 10)
  - Brel is Alive, "Marieke", undated (Box 262, Folder 11)
  - Brel is Alive, "Mathilde", undated (Box 262, Folder 12)
  - Brel is Alive, "My Death", undated (Box 262, Folder 13)
  - Brel is Alive, "Next", undated (Box 262, Folder 14)
  - Brel is Alive, "Old Folks", undated (Box 262, Folder 15)
  - Brel is Alive, "Sons of...", undated (Box 262, Folder 16)
  - Brel is Alive, "Timid Frieda", undated (Box 262, Folder 17)
  - Brel is Alive, "You're Not Alone", undated (Box 262, Folder 18)
  - Brel is Alive, Bass Parts, undated (Box 262, Folder 19)
  - Brel is Alive, Guitar Parts, undated (Box 262, Folder 20)
  - Brel is Alive, Percussion Parts, undated (Box 262, Folder 21)
  - Brel is Alive, Piano Parts, undated (Box 262, Folder 22)
  - Theatre Arrangements, undated (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Fiddler on the Roof Parts, undated (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - "Mireles Erklehrung" and "Marcus Solo", undated (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Rothschilds Master Track, undated (Box 263, Folder 4)
    Includes one 1/4 inch audiotape.
  - Rothschilds Loose Parts, undated (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Rothschilds Piano Conductor Score, undated (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Rothschilds Vocal Selections Songbook, undated (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Various Lead Sheets, undated (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - A New Day Tape Recording, 1969 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - A New Day Album Notes, 1969 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - A New Day, "For No One", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - A New Day, "I Hear the Laughter", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - A New Day, "Jennifer Juniper", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - A New Day, "The Lady is Waiting", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - A New Day, "Lady Jane", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - A New Day, "Love My Dog", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - A New Day, "Mother Nature's Son", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - A New Day, "Piggies", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 10)
  - A New Day, "The Urge for Going", 1969 (Box 264, Folder 11)
  - Silent No More Materials, 1970 (Box 264, Folder 12)
  - "Amsterdam", undated (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - "Great Mandella", undated (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - "Hava Nageela", undated (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - "My Old Pal", undated (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - "Shabat Shalom", undated (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - "Those Were the Days", undated (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - "We Are One", 1974 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - "What's That I Hear", undated (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - "Zephania", undated (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Shabat Shira Fund Event, 1973-4 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Parts, undated (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Published Songs, undated (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Various Club Parts, undated (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Various Lead Sheets, undated (Box 266, Folder 5-6)
  - Various Parts - 2nd Halves, undated (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Various Piano and Vocal Parts, undated (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Russian Materials Music, undated (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Russian Materials Writing, undated (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Dov Seltzer, Song of Songs Part I, "The Lovers", 1963 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Dov Seltzer, Song of Songs Part II, "The Abduction", 1963 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Dov Seltzer, Song of Songs Part III, "The Escape", 1963 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - "The 42nd" and "Haulaway Joe", undated (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - "Erev Shel Shoshanim", undated (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - "Flowers", undated (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Folksinger's Choice Accordion Parts, undated (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Folksinger's Choice Banjo Parts, undated (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Folksinger's Choice Bass Parts, undated (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Folksinger's Choice Guitar Parts, undated (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Folksinger's Choice Recorder Parts, undated (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - Fiddler On the Roof Piano Conductor Scores, undated (Box 268, Folder 9)
  - "Get Up Get Out", undated (Box 268, Folder 10)
  - "Haleluyah", undated (Box 268, Folder 11)
  - Harvest of Israeli Songs, undated (Box 268, Folder 12)
  - "Jerusalem", undated (Box 268, Folder 13)
  - "Man Come Into Egypt", undated (Box 268, Folder 14)
  - "Old Folks", undated (Box 268, Folder 15)
  - Published Sheet Music, undated (Box 268, Folder 16)
  - "Russian Gypsy", undated (Box 268, Folder 17)
  - "September Song", undated (Box 268, Folder 18)
  - "Sunrise Sunset", undated (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - "Those Were the Days", undated (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - "Time In a Bottle", undated (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - "The Vision of Isaiah", undated (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Various Drum Parts, undated (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Various Bass Parts, undated (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Various Parts, undated (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - Various Piano Parts, undated (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - Various Violin Parts, undated (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - "A Chasene Tants", undated (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - "Great Mandella", undated (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man", undated (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - "Mack the Knife", undated (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - "Marieke", undated (Box 270, Folder 5-6)
  - Miscellaneous Jewish Music, undated (Box 270, Folder 7-9)
  - Miscellaneous Pages, undated (Box 271, Folder 1-2)
  - Various Orchestral Parts, undated (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Various Parts, undated (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Various Piano Conductor Parts, undated (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Various Scores, undated (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - "With a Little Bit of Luck", undated (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - Various Conductor Scores, undated (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - "Al Naharot, On the River of Babylon", undated (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - "The Creation of the World", undated (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - "The Vision of Isaiah", undated (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - "The Vision of the Bones", undated (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - 18th Jewish Choral Festival, 2007 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Kings and Fishermen, 2000 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - "Chanson des vieux amants", 2006 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - "Durme Durme", undated (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Chanukah at Grover's Corner, 1992 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Fab 4 Theo, undated (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Harvest Materials, 1967 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man", undated (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - "Man Come Into Egypt", undated (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Folk Music, undated (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Jewish Songs, undated (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Parts, undated (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Scores, undated (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Songs, undated (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Jewish Songs, undated (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - "Yiddish Suite", undated (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - "The Bitter and the Sweet", undated (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - "Bublichky", undated (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - "Dire Geld", undated (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - "Got Fun Avrum", undated (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - "Guajira", undated (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - "Ich Bin Farlibt", undated (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - "A KIein Melamedl", undated (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - "Man Into Egypt", undated (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - "Milners Tretren", undated (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - Poster/"The Times They are A-Changin'" Lyrics, undated (Box 275, Folder 10)
  - "Reb Tevye", undated (Box 275, Folder 11)
  - "Amsterdam" and others, undated (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - "The Sun Also Sets" and others, undated (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - "Skins" opening, undated (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Hellerman scores, undated (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - "Shvu'a" (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - "Eten Bamidbar" (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - "Amsterdam", undated (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - Songbooks and lyrics binders, 1977-1990 (Box 278, Folder 1-8)
- Series 3: Scripts and screenplays, 1951-2014
  Series contains scripts and screenplays for stage, film, and television projects. Multiple copies of The Gathering are annotated.
  - About Time, 1991 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - The African Queen, 1951 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Altman's Last Stand, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Antigone, undated (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - The August Coup, undated (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Babylon 5 - "In the Beginning", 1997 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - The Bayonet, undated (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Babylon 5 - "TKO", 1994 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - A Beloved Teacher, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Benefit of the Doubt, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Benya the King, undated (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Born Guilty, 1994 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - The Bridge of Trust, 2002 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Bring a Rock to Israel, 1981 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn South, 1997 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Buck James - "Almost Perfect", 1987 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - The Burning Zone, 1996 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Chassidism or The Joyful Path to God, circa 1967 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Jewish Video Project, undated (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - The Chosen, undated (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Christine Cromwell - In Vino Veritas, 1989 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Conversations with my Father, 1992 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Crime and Punishment, 1993 (Box 213, Folder 1-2)
  - Crisis in the Kremlin, 1991 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Death and Taxes, 1997 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Die Disputation, 1997 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - The Disputation, 1998-2005 (Box 213, Folder 6-7)
  - The Disputation notes, 1995-1998 (Box 214, Folder 1-2)
  - A Dog of Flanders, 1959 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Doolittle, 2014 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Drawn and Quartered, 1992 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - The Dream, 1997 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - The Dybbuk, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Dying Things, 1986-1994 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Eli, the Fanatic, undated (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - The Family Jewels, 1992 (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - Fiddler on the Roof, undated (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Fiddler on the Roof, undated (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - The Fifth Cup, 1992-1993 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - The Flowering Peach, 1954 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - A Friend of Kafka, undated (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - The Gathering, 1997 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - The Gathering, 1999 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - The Gathering, 1999 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - The Gathering notes, 1998-1999 (Box 215, Folder 7-8)
  - Goldenrod, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - The Golden Ladder, 1995 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - Greetings...Sholom Aleichem Lives!, 1997 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Harris Newmark's Los Angeles - The Los Angeles History Project, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Herzl Readings, undated (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - H.U.D., 2000 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - If All Danes Were Jews, 1996 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Inside the Soviet Circus, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - In the Name of Love, God, and Marjorie Morningstar, undated (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - In the Right Hand of God the Father, undated (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Jag "The Big Show", 2003 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - A Jewish Perspective, 1961 (Box 229, Folder 9)
  - Joy Beyond Measure, undated (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - The Labor of Life, undated (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - The Lady's Not for Burning, circa 1975 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Law and Order "Snatched", 2003 (Box 216, Folder 12)
  - Lean on the Wind, undated (Box 216, Folder 13)
  - Life in Refusal, 2003 (Box 216, Folder 14)
  - The Little Men Di Kleine Mentchalach, undated (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - The Little Traitor, undated (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - The Lost Wooden Synagogues of Eastern Europe, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Lovers and Strangers, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Manny's War, 2003 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - The Marriage Contract, 2006 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Murder She Wrote "Amsterdam Kill", 1994 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Murder She Wrote "The List of Uri Lermentov", 1991 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - The Mysteries of the Cabala, undated (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Next Year in Jerusalem, 1993 (Box 217, Folder 10)
  - Orson notes, 1993 (Box 217, Folder 11)
  - Outta Sight, 1986-1987 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Pace, undated (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Payday, 1997 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Park Wellington, undated (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - The Passover Story, 1992 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - The Pious Rascal, 1992 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - The Pious Scoundrel, 1993 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - The Pretender, 1997 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - The Prince of Schnorrers, 1999-2001 (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - The Prince of Schnorrers notes, 1999-2001 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Roma Romani, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Remembering the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Sabina, 1993 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Second Chances, 1997 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Sholom Aleichem: Laughter through Tears, undated (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Shylock, 2005 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Sidney Sheldon's "Memories of Midnight", 1991 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - A Song without Words, 2003 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Spring Forward, Fall Back, 2004 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Staus, 1982 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - The Substance of Fire, 1991 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - The Sunshine Boys, undated (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - The Talking Cure, 2001 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - A Taste of Passover, undated (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - The Threepenny Opera, 1998 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Tuesdays with Morrie, 2002 (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Untitled Wolfgang Petersen Project, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - The Value of Names, undated (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - The Value of Names notes, undated (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Voices of Leningrad, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - The Wayfarers, 2003 (Box 221, Folder 5)
- Series 4: Photographs, 1950s-2006
  Photographs are primarily 8 x 10 black-and-white performance photographs, stills, and publicity portraits.
  - Performances and stills, circa 1953-1990s (Box 230, Folder 1-8)
    Includes images from Fiddler on the Roof, The Defiant Ones, The Kidnappers, Darker Than Amber, Ironsides, The Enemy Below, and Babylon 5 (snapshots).
  - Publicity portraits, bulk 1960s (Box 230, Folder 9-17)
    Includes headshots (signed copies in folder 9), and music performance shots, both with and without guitar.
  - 1968 Democratic Convention, Chicago (Box 230, Folder 18)
  - Bikel with Bill and Hillary Clinton, 1990s (Box 230, Folder 19)
  - Loose photographs and snapshots, 1969-2006 (Box 230, Folder 20-23)
    Also includes some contact sheets and copies of photographs.
  - Photograph albums/ scrapbooks, circa 1988-2002 (Box 231)
- Series 5: Memorabilia, 1944-2014
  THIS SERIES CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Scrapbooks, 1951-1956 (Box 279, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1957-1959, 1963-1964 (Box 280, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1958-1959 (Box 281, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1960-1961 (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1961-1963 (Box 283, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1968-1972 (Box 284, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1966-1978 (Box 285, Folder 1-2)
  - The 1969 Warner - Reprise Record Show booklet (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Publications and clippings, 1959-2008 (Box 286, Folder 1-5)
  - Performance ephemera, 1944-2014 (Box 287, Folder 1-5)
  - Performance ephemera, 1967-2011 (Box 288, Folder 1-6)
  - Performance ephemera, 1975-2010 (Box 289, Folder 1-6)
    THIS BOX CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Awards, 1988-2005 (Box 290, Folder 1-6)
  - Awards, 1960-2009 (Box 291, Folder 1-7)
  - Awards, 1961-2013 (Box 292, Folder 1-7)
  - Awards, 1960-2014 (Box 293, Folder 1-3)
- Series 6: Audiovisual material, 1957-2014